Legislative Correspondents Association of New York State; Records apap357
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- LCA Show, 1902-2024; 7.89 cubic ft.
  - Possible Television Coverage of Show, Unidentified, Undated (Umatic 24)
  - Rough Draft of Show Program, by Ed Murawinski, Undated (Flat-file 6)
  - Scripts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Second Act of Show, Undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Show Photo Album (1 of 2), Undated (Oversized 2)
  - Show Photo Album (2 of 2), Undated (Oversized 2)
  - Show Photos A-E, Undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Show Photos (1 of 2), Undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Show Photos (2 of 2), Undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Small Show Photo Album, Undated (Oversized 2)
- Reference and Subject Files, 1900-1994; .9 cubic ft.
  This series contains reference material that may have been used by the correspondents when researching topics for a story. It also contains subject files of Ray Borst and Robert Fusco, who were very active throughout their professional lives in the LCA. Some of Robert Fusco's articles are housed in a seperate flate file.
  The flat file that contains the article "Corruption Uncorked in New York" is part of the file labeled "Kisburg-Gruntner Key Incident."
  - Analysis of New York Governors and Legislatures, 1900-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Reception to Hon. James J. Walker, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - In Memoriam of Perley A. Pitcher, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Testimonial Dinner Program to Thomas C. Stowell, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Voter Registration, Votes Cast, and Press Releases, 1950-1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Cities Enrollment, 1950-1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Life Magazine Article, "Corruption Uncorked in New York", 1963 (Flat-file 7)
  - Ray Borst Papers, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "The Republican Record", 1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Kisburg-Grutner Senate Key Incident, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Jack Troy Photograph, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Robert Fusco Papers (1 of 2), 1966-1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Robert Fusco Papers (2 of 2), 1966-1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Neil Kelleher Photographs, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Voter Registration and Votes Cast, 1966; 1969-1970; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "As Hy Rosen Saw It", 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Matteo Retrospective of Journalist Reporting at Capital, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - News Conference of Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Congressional District Maps #2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 9, 10, 11, 1970 (Flat-file 8)
  - News Releases about 200th Anniversary of American Revolution and a Copy of the Correspondent, 1969; 1972; 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Research Materials, News Articles, 1970; 1971; 1972; Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - New York State Senate and Assembly Vote Totals, 1972; 1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Voter Registration, Votes Cast, and Press Releases (1 of 2), 1972; 1974-1982; Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Voter Registration, Votes Cast, and Press Releases (2 of 2), 1972; 1974-1982; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - News Releases and Statistics of Board of Elections, 1973-1975; 1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - News Reporters Covering the New York State Legislature, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Election Newsletter Ballot Billboard, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - New York State Primary Results and Press Releases, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Lemon Law Pamphlet, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Voter Registration, Votes Cast, and Press Releases, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report of the New York State Standing Committee on Insurance, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Department of Agriculture and Markets Report, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - John Nelson Papers, 1987; 1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - News Release, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Speech Bubble, Signed, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - New York State Assembly Presents Chateau on the Hill, 1992 (Vhs 20)
  - PIO Directory of State Agency Contact Personnel, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Edward F. McDonough Election Pamphlet, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Jane Barton News Release, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Lobbyist Labels, Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Pamphlet About Albany and New York State, Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Press Photo, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Reporters Notes From Press Conference, Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Rough Draft of an Article on the Murder of Scarsdale Diet Doctor, Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Robert Fusco's Articles, Undated (Flat-file 9)